

Xing Tian

Profile

Full stack software developer, with experience working as a front end developer and web UI developer, I am a person who is passionate about technology and loves to learn new things every day, I am characterized for being responsible, proactive and creative. Who can contribute great things to a work team, I adapt easily to new challenges and seek solutions to problems that arise sporadically. I firmly believe that currently if we can imagine, we can program it.

Employment History

Senior Full-Stack Developer, Aura Tech

MARCH 2023 — PRESENT

- Worked as Full Stack Web Developer for various projects.
- Worked on speed optimization by minimizing JavaScript, CSS and merging files to reduce request count.
- Implemented JavaScript load on request.
- Implemented caching files which don't change often, To reduce the load on the server.
- Followed best practices for speed optimizations like making JavaScript request at the end after all other requests.

Full-Stack Developer, Jacob Jensen Design A/S

DECEMBER 2022 — MARCH 2023

- Developed full-stack web applications which processed, analyzed, and rendered data visually.
- Liaised with back end developers, front end developers, quality assurance testers, and CTO as needed.
- Spearheaded transition from LAMP stack to MERN, MEVN, MEAN stack, reducing latency by 50% and increasing database admin effectiveness by 25%.

Blockchain Developer, WEBSAILORS.PRO, Taganrog

AUGUST 2021 — DECEMBER 2022

- Cryptocurrency exchange development
- Cryptocurrency coin and token creation
- Smart contract development
- Blockchain app and DAPP development
- NFT marketplace design and development
- Decentralized Finance (DEFI) development
- Custom cryptocurrency, Blockchain, NFT app development, and more.

Details

No.123, Xixi Road, Xihu District, Hangzhou, Zhejiang Province, China

NATIONALITY

Chinese

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

9.21.1994 Hang Zhou, China

Skills

REACT/REDUX/HOOK

VUE/VUEX

Next.js

Node.js

Django

Laravel

Amazon AWS

Git

MySQL/MongoDB/PostgreSQL

Blockchain

Smart contract

solidity

web3.js

Hobbies

FootBall

Languages

English

Chinese

Education

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, Zhejiang University, China

APRIL 2015 — OCTOBER 2017